okay I've written here that aqua 14 will
be the shift in the trash cycle and I
don't think that necessarily is one apt
necessarily certainly one out
necessarily it's a lot of necessarily
but having a way to track what we choose
to buy what that creates myspace harder
to turn it off knockouts shift and
wretch cycle um exactly more of those
following the trashy make what your city
does with it I mean I guess we're
talking about that now this was a
different thing but oh so I mean I
recycle I try to recycle everything I
can in my compost but it goes to the
city for composting I don't compost in
my backyard and I try to minimize that a
waste I have but I don't know I don't
know where the recycling actually goes
what it gets made into you know and so
being able to track that be able to say
okay if I have this object what went
into it how long do I have to own it to
justify owning it what I mean by that is
people talk about having like you have a
to-go container for coffee versus your
own coffee cup using it every day it's
clearly better to have the coffee cup
that you can reuse but if you forget it
and you're oh is it better to buy a new
one and have to or to buy the to-go cup
and how many cups of the to go have to
go into the permanent one or usable one
to equal the energy the human time the
resources to go into it to equal just
getting it to go to go cup sometimes it
probably is a better option so being
able to see that being able to see how
our choices and what we buy based on
what they're created out of and what
they can be what they can become is what
that means so we can follow the charge
cycle
understand it right